when when my wife was pregnant with my
daughter she was so scared she was
terrified of the delivery you know the
birth and she handled it like a champ
and I knew she would I wasn't surprised
I knew she'd she'd do it great because
it's true what they say about women
right
women women have an extremely high
tolerance for pain it's insane
which i think is kind of weird
considering they're such a low tolerance
for mild inconvenience
[Applause]
you can just stood up he's sleeping on
the couch for a feel it's weird though
it's true you know my wife she can push
a 9-pound baby through the inside of her
body but heaven forbid Hulu Plus has
commercials subscribe to drive our
comedy for even more of the world's
largest collection of clean comedy